all of the objections we get,
objection by objection, and exactly what to save.
So what does this look like? So you've,
you've offered the package, how does that sound?
21 Day Kickstart, how does that sound? Or it's,
I'm not too, I'm not too sure,
it's a little bit expensive, I don't know if I can afford it,
it's too expensive, I don't get paid yet.
I'm not too sure, etc.
So, depending on the kind of price objection will
dictate what you do and I'm gonna create a flow chart for all of
these to really visualize it nicely. So,
the best price related objection is simply,
oh, I don't get paid until next week,
until next Tuesday, until next Thursday,
until next Friday. That's really easy.
All you simply do is something called a delayed payment close.
So, you just tell them, no worries at all, John.
What we can do is we'll start next week,
we'll book in a time for you to call with Jamie,
and then you can sort it out then when you get paid.
Is that cool? So,
if they are telling you they just simply can't afford it now,
but they can afford it next week, do that.
If they say, oh, I'm not getting paid until next week,
don't just be like, no worries. Say,
okay, what day next week do you get paid?
And then book in a session.
Then, okay. You always want to book in,
sorry, book in a call then. You always want to book in a call
or a catch up or just, just a day for us to follow up
to get that payment. Can't afford it right now,
do a delayed payment.
Any other price objection, you're going to have to handle it now.
So, what do we do before we do an objection?
We use the understanding framework.
We're like, look, I understand, it's a lot of money.
John, is, is that the only thing stopping you from starting our Kickstarter right
now? Yes. Okay,
if we could talk through that, if we could work something out.
Is there a possibility of you joining us for our Kickstarter program?
Yeah, probably, which is what they usually say.
Well, then let's talk about it.
So, John, this is a lot of money for you,
isn't it? Yes. And I'm glad that it's a lot of money for you.
I'd be more concerned if this wasn't a lot of money for you.
Because then I think you wouldn't even try. You know,
our best client testimonials,
success stories, and victories are all from people who this was a lot of
money for. Because if this is a lot of money for you,
does that mean you're going to work really hard? Yes.
Well, then you shouldn't be worried about seeing results.
Yeah, true. If that works,
go through with the payment. If not,
keep going. So, because, does that mean you're working really hard?
Yes. Then you're the last person who should be worried about seeing results because
this means a lot to you, doesn't it? True.
Well, then let's get started. Bang,
tap. Yeah, it's still,
don't know. Okay, look, John. If I told you that I could help you
learn and be on track to achieve XYZ goals,
if I told you we could help you lose the weight,
build the muscle, learn how to train for a tenth of the price.
Would you really believe me? Probably not.
Okay. Well, then clearly it's not just about the price then.
Maybe it's just you are concerned about whether it's going to work for you
or not. Let's just make sure we're clear here.
These are some of the things we do to make sure that you get
what you want. So, we help you keep incredibly accountable.
We give you the tools to succeed. We give you a training program.
We give you the meal guidance, etc.
But we hold you accountable, John. We're not going to let you give up
on yourself. That's what we're here for. It's about that accountability and support that
is going to allow you to really accelerate your progress in the next 21
days. I'm going to make sure you do your training program.
I'm going to make sure you eat the right foods. I'm going to make
sure you push yourself hard enough in and out of the sessions with
our app. Do you see how with that level of accountability,
you're pretty much guaranteed succeed with us,
John? Yes. Are you ready to move forward?
Okay, let me break this down. So, the first thing is,
you want to, you want to acknowledge there's a lot of money for them,
and you're basically just telling them, like, that's a good thing.
We're reframing it. It's a good thing it's a lot of money for them,
because it means that they're actually going to try harder.
You know, how many members have a gym membership and don't go to the
gym? Most of them. Because it's not a lot for them.
Because this is a lot for these people,
It means I'll actually try harder. But really,
if it's not a lot for them, they probably won't show up anyway.
So, it's a good thing. And what that means is that they're going to
get better results. Plus,
if this means a lot to them as well, you know,
if it is actually important to them to lose weight,
if it is important for them to build strength,
then that means it's even more important, and they're going to work even harder.
transitioning to value. Realistically,
guys, if this was $3 a week, would people try?
Would people believe us that we could help them teach them how to build
confidence in the gym, lose a few kilos in those three weeks,
build confidence? No, they wouldn't.
And if that's the truth, well then price isn't the issue then.
It's just they think that it's not going to work.
They're scared they're going to make a mistake. And that's when you reassure them
that we help them with incredible levels of accountability and support.
And you finish that up with, are you ready to move?
So.
if they're still not budging, then of course what you do is you book
them in for a call with me because if they don't sign up,
you book them in for a call with me and then I'll work on
that. But that's how you handle price objections.